[Music]
English listening test part four
designed for A1
Learners this test consists of 20
questions which are divided into four
parts I will give you a short
instruction at the beginning of each
part before we get started take a pen
and paper so you can take notes while
listening are you ready
let's get
started part one listen to two
conversations and take
notes hi are you a
member no I'm just here for the
day okay so what's your name please
Graham is that g r a h a m no it's g r a
m e
okay thanks and what's your phone number
it's
82013 right yeah that's it and your
email address um it's grr Smith
37@gmail.com
so it's $15 for today here's your pass
thanks
Hi how are you doing pretty good how
about you good thanks it's a beautiful
day yeah it is are you here for the
concert I wish I were I'm waiting for my
friend to work on a project how about
you well yeah but I'm a student here too
by the way I'm Ryan I'm Bailey nice to
meet you well have a nice day thanks you
too choose the correct
[Music]
option
part two listen to people ordering food
and drinks in a cafe and answer the true
or false
questions
can I have an apple juice
please regular or
large how big is a large this is regular
and this is large I would like a regular
drink please could you also add some ice
to it okay coming
up sorry I wanted freshly squeezed apple
juice I'm afraid we only have bottled
juices oh then I'll have an orange juice
instead please here you go that's $4.50
cents please
thanks can I help you sir what types of
coffee do you have espresso iced coffee
Americano and Latte a latte and a slice
of chocolate cake
please to eat in or take away take away
please
there you go that'll be
$620 please sorry I've only got a 50
that's okay here's your change 5 20 30
50 who's next can I have a chocolate
chip cookie please would you like a
drink with that no thanks just the
cookie okay then that's $95 please
thanks I think that's right 50 70 8085
90 yep
95 thank
you true or
false
[Music]
part three listen to Rachel talking
about more members of her family and
answer the true or false
questions this is Martha she's my sister
older sister or younger sister older
where does she live in the city center
she lives with her husband and her baby
baby boy ah what's her baby's name Brad
He's lovely oh so is Martha a housewife
no she's a teacher she works in a school
in the city center she's a Spanish
teacher that's amazing and this is Adam
he's my favorite cousin wow he's nice I
know he lives in San
Francisco oh no why he's an actor well
he's an actor and a waiter he works in a
French restaurant but he's a very good
actor is he married no he isn't married
but he's got lovely friends how often do
you see him I see him twice a
year true or
false
[Music]
part four listen to a story about Jack
preparing food and be ready to answer
the questions that
follow Jack was hungry so he walked to
the kitchen first he got out some eggs
and took out some oil then he placed a
skillet on the stove and turned on the
he
he poured the oil into the skillet next
he cracked the eggs into a bowl and
stirred them after that he poured them
into the hot Skillet he patiently waited
as the eggs were being cooked they were
cooked in two minutes he heard them
cooking they popped in the
oil next Jack put the eggs on a plate he
placed the plate on the dining room
table which was made of steel Jack loved
looking looking at the eggs they looked
pretty on the white plate he sat down on
a large wooden chair he thought about
the day ahead he ate the eggs with a
spoon they were good he washed the plate
with dishwashing soap then he washed the
pan he got a sponge damp finally he
wiped down the table and went to watch
TV choose the correct
option
[Music]
oh
don't forget to share your score in the
comments
section if you haven't taken our
previous listening tests the playlist
link is in the description
below we will upload more listening
tests so don't forget to subscribe and
stay tuned see you in our upcoming
videos